Finding Aid for the Collection of Broadside Ballads from England, Ireland, and the United States LSC.0605
UCLA Library Special Collections
- England
  - Smith, 18--
    - Cruel Angelina: or, The broken-down baker. Haydon, James, Cruel Angelina: or, The broken-down baker. London, England; Smith, Printer, Broadway, Westminster, [18--]., Shelfmark: 3:14:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 20 cm. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Spencer, 18--
    Printed in Bradford, England.
    - Plough boy. Ballinafad. O…Keeffe, John, 1747-1833, The plough boy. Bradford, England; Spencer, Broadstones, Bradford, [18--]., Shelfmark: 6:7:20; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 24 × 18 cm. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Plough boy. Ballinafad. Ballinafad. Bradford, England; Spencer, Broadstones, Bradford, [18--]., Shelfmark: 6:7:20; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 24 × 18 cm. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Stevens, Thomas, ca. 1750-1850
    Printed in Bristol, England.
    - Jacob's return from London: or, His ramble to Bath / written and delivered by Mr. Knight, at the Theatre, Bath. Knight, T. (Thomas), d. 1820, Jacob's return from London: or, His ramble to Bath / written and delivered by Mr. Knight, at the Theatre, Bath. Bristol, England; Printed by Thomas Stevens Store No. 4, Norrow-Wine-Street Bristol, [between 1750 and 1850]., Shelfmark: Stevens; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 23 × 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Stevenson and Matchett, 18--
    Printed in Norwich, England.
    - Loyal subject's political creed: or, What I do & what I do not believe. The loyal subject's political creed: or, What I do & what I do not believe. Norwich, England; Stevenson, Matchett, and Stevenson, Printers, Market-place, Norwich, [18--]., Shelfmark: Stevenson; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 21 × 15 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Such, Henry Parker (Address-Cottage), ca. 1849-1885
    - Address of unemployed workmen. I. The tradesman's lament. II. One God made us all. The tradesman's lament. London, England; Such, Printer, 177, Union Street, Borough, [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 8:8:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Address of unemployed workmen. I. The tradesman's lament. II. One God made us all. One God made us all. London, England; Such, Printer, 177, Union Street, Borough, [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 8:8:11; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - American stranger. Polly's love: or, The cruel ship carpenter. Polly's love: or, The cruel ship carpenter. London, England; H. Such, Printer, 123, Union Street, Boro' S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3:1:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - American stranger. Polly's love: or, The cruel ship carpenter. American stranger. London, England; H. Such, Printer, 123, Union Street, Boro' S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3:1:10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Ashantee war: or, A soldier's farewell. Mother's far away. Mother's far away. London, England; London: H. Such, Machine Printer, & Publisher 177, Union Street, Boro'., S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:2:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Ashantee war: or, A soldier's farewell. Mother's far away. Ashantee War: or, A soldier's farewell. London, England; London: H. Such, Machine Printer, & Publisher 177, Union Street, Boro'., S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:2:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Barrel of pork. Poor married man. The barrel of pork. London, England; London: Printed and sold by H. Such. 123, Union Street, Boro', S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3:3:12; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Barrel of pork. Poor married man. Hardwick, J. A., Poor married man. London, England; London: Printed and sold by H. Such. 123, Union Street, Boro', S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3:3:12; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Batchelor's [sic] wants. Creeping Jane. Youd, John, A batchelor's [sic] wants. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer & Publisher, 177, Union Street, Borough, S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:3:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Batchelor's [sic] wants. Creeping Jane. Creeping Jane. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer & Publisher, 177, Union Street, Borough, S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:3:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bay of Biscay. Bill Jones. Cherry, A. (Andrew), 1762-1812, The Bay of Biscay. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer and Publisher 177, Union Street, Borough. S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:3:19; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bay of Biscay. Bill Jones. Bill Jones. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer and Publisher 177, Union Street, Borough. S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:3:19; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bessy Bloom, the flower girl! Bessy Bloom, the flower girl!. London, England; London: Printed and Sold by H. Such, 123, Union Street, Boro'. S.E. and at 33, WhiteCross-st, St. Luke's, [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3:4:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 10 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Best of friends must part. The little church round the corner. The best of friends must part. London, England; London, H.P. Such, Machine Printer, and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Borough, [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:4:18; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Best of friends must part. The little church round the corner. The little church round the corner. London, England; London, H.P. Such, Machine Printer, and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Borough, [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:4:18; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Blackbird and thrush. The old arbour tree. The blackbird and thrush. London, England; London: H.P. Such, Machine Printer Publisher, 177, Union-st., Boro', [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:5:12; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Blackbird and thrush. The old arbour tree. The old arbour tree. London, England; London: H.P. Such, Machine Printer Publisher, 177, Union-st., Boro', [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:5:12; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Black-smith. Burns' farewell. Burns, Robert, 1759-1796, Burns' farewell. London, England; London: H. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro'., S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:5:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 20 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Black-smith. Burns' farewell. Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth, 1807-1882, Black-smith. London, England; London: H. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro'., S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:5:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 20 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Blind beggar's daughter of Bethnal Green. Castle Hyde. Blind beggar's daughter of Bethnal Green. London, England; London: Printed at Such's Song Mart, 123, Union Street, Boro', S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3:5:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Blind beggar's daughter of Bethnal Green. Castle Hyde. Castle Hyde. London, England; London: Printed at Such's Song Mart, 123, Union Street, Boro', S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3:5:15; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Blind boy. The banks of Claudy. Cook, Eliza, 1818-1889, The blind boy. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer & Publisher 177, Union-st., Boro,' S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:5:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Blind boy. The banks of Claudy. The banks of Claudy. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer & Publisher 177, Union-st., Boro,' S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:5:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bold Robin Hood. The blackbird. Bold Robin Hood. London, England; H. P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro', S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:7:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 18 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bold Robin Hood. The blackbird. The blackbird. London, England; H. P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro', S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:7:1; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 18 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - British soldier's grave. Baby mine. A British soldier's grave. [London], [England], [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:7:18; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - British soldier's grave. Baby mine. Mackay, Charles, 1814-1889, Baby mine. [London], [England], [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:7:18; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bunch of rushes. The queer little man. The queer little man. London, England; H. P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Borough, S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:8:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bunch of rushes. The queer little man. The bunch of rushes. London, England; H. P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Borough, S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:8:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Burial club. Isle of beauty, fare-thee-well. Isle of beauty, fare-thee-well. London, England; London: H. P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union-street Borough, S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:8:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Burial club. Isle of beauty, fare-thee-well. Burial club. London, England; London: H. P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union-street Borough, S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:8:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Cast aside. The old miser. The old miser. London, England; London: H. Such, Machine Printer & Publisher, 177, Union-st., Boro', [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:9:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Cast aside. The old miser. Cast aside. London, England; London: H. Such, Machine Printer & Publisher, 177, Union-st., Boro', [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:9:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Charming young widow I met in the train. Cove, W. H., The charming young widow I met in the train. London, England; London, H.P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Borough, S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:9:17; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Close the ale-house door. Close the ale-house door. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro.' S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:10:18; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Colleen Bawn. My native land so green. My native land so green. London, England; London: H. Such, Machine printer, & publisher, 177, Union-street, Boro'., S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:11:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Colleen Bawn. My native land so green. Boucicault, Dion, 1820-1890, The colleen bawn. London, England; London: H. Such, Machine printer, & publisher, 177, Union-street, Boro'., S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:11:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Come under my plaidie. Macneill, Hector, 1746-1818, Come under my plaidie. London, England; London: H.P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro'. S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:12:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Cottage by the sea. Free and easy. Sydney, Harry, Free and easy. London, England; London: H.P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union-street, Borough, [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:13:7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Cottage by the sea. Free and easy. Thomas, J. R. (John Rogers), 1830-1896, The cottage by the sea. London, England; London: H.P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union-street, Borough, [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:13:7; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Such, Henry Parker (Country-Female), ca. 1849-1885
    - Country lass. Be careful in choosing a wife. Old England forever shall weather the storm. Old England for ever shall weather the storm. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer & Publisher, 177, (late 123), Union Street, Boro', [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:13:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Country lass. Be careful in choosing a wife. Old England forever shall weather the storm. Be careful in choosing a wife. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer & Publisher, 177, (late 123), Union Street, Boro', [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:13:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Country lass. Be careful in choosing a wife. Old England forever shall weather the storm. The country lass. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer & Publisher, 177, (late 123), Union Street, Boro', [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:13:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Cruel miller. Silly young maid. Cruel miller. London, England; London: H.P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro', [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:14:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Cruel miller. Silly young maid. Silly young maid. London, England; London: H.P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro', [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:14:3; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Cruiskeen lawn. Boucicault, Dion, 1820-1890, Cruiskeen lawn. London, England; London: Printed and Published by H. Such, 123, Union street, Boro' S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3:14:5; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 17 × 8 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Dawning of the day. The Duke of Marlborough. Dawning of the day. London, England; London: Printed at Such's Song Mart, 123, Union Street, Boro'. S.E. and at 83, Upper White Cross-street, St. Luke's, [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3:15:12; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Dawning of the day. The Duke of Marlborough. The Duke of Marlborough. London, England; London: Printed at Such's Song Mart, 123, Union Street, Boro'. S.E. and at 83, Upper White Cross-street, St. Luke's, [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3:15:12; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Day that we got wed. Why everything's so precious dear that's what I want to know. The day that we got wed. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer and Publisher 177, Union Street, Borough, S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:15:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Day that we got wed. Why everything's so precious dear that's what I want to know. Why everything's so precious dear that's what I want to know. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer and Publisher 177, Union Street, Borough, S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:15:13; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Dear Father come home. Work, Henry C. (Henry Clay), 1832-1884, Dear Father come home. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer, 177, Union-st., Boro', [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:15:14; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 17 × 9 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Dear Italy! Ranawail. The mantle of green. The mantle of green. London, England; London: Printed at Such's Song Mart, 123, Union Street, Boro', S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3:15:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Dear Italy! Ranawail. The mantle of green. Dear Italy!. London, England; London: Printed at Such's Song Mart, 123, Union Street, Boro', S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3:15:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Dear Italy! Ranawail. The mantle of green. Ranawail. London, England; London: Printed at Such's Song Mart, 123, Union Street, Boro', S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3:15:16; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Dear young girls: parody on "Dear old pals". Dear young girls: parody on "Dear old pals". London, England; H.P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, "177," Union-street, Borough, [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:15:18; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 18 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Death of Black Bess. High Germany. High Germany. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer, & Publisher, 177 (late 123), Union street, Boro.' S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:16:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Death of Black Bess. High Germany. Death of Black Bess. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer, & Publisher, 177 (late 123), Union street, Boro.' S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:16:2; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Deeds of Napoleon. Isle of St. Helena. Isle of St. Helena. London, England; London: H. Such, Machine Printer & Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro'. S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:16:7; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Deeds of Napoleon. Isle of St. Helena. Deeds of Napoleon. London, England; London: H. Such, Machine Printer & Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro'. S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3:16:7; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Dodger: or, fare-ye-vell, my Vitechapel boys. Live and let live. Cook, Eliza, 1818-1889, Live and let live. London, England; London: H. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro., S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3.17.6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 18 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Dodger: or, fare-ye-vell, my Vitechapel boys. Live and let live. The dodger: or, Fare-ye-vell, my Vitechapel boys. London, England; London: H. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro., S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3.17.6; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 18 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Down among the dead men. Mill May. 'Tis but a little faded flower. Enoch, Frederick, 'Tis but a little faded flower. London, England; London: H.P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union-street, Borough, [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3.17.11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Down among the dead men. Mill May. 'Tis but a little faded flower. Dyer, John, 1700?-1758, Down among the dead men. London, England; London: H.P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union-street, Borough, [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3.17.11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Down among the dead men. Mill May. 'Tis but a little faded flower. Mill May. London, England; London: H.P. Such, Machine Printer and Publisher, 177, Union-street, Borough, [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 3.17.11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Drunken husband. Paddy from Cork!: with his coat buttoned behind. The drunken husband. London, England; London: Printed at Such's Song Mart, 123, Union Street, Borough, [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3.18.10; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Drunken husband. Paddy from Cork!: with his coat buttoned behind. Paddy from Cork!: with his coat buttoned behind. London, England; London: Printed at Such's Song Mart, 123, Union Street, Borough, [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 3.18.10; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Erin's blooming Jane. The Shannon side. Erin's blooming Jane. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer, 123, Union Street, Boro., S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 4.2.17; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 20 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Erin's blooming Jane. The Shannon side. The Shannon side. London, England; London: H. Such, Printer, 123, Union Street, Boro., S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 4.2.17; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 20 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Fair shines the moon tonight. Fair shines the moon tonight. London, England; H. Such, Printer & c., 123, Union Street, Borough, London, [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 4.4.7; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 16 × 8 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Faithful Ellen. The little town's boy. The little town's boy. London, England; London: Printed and published by H. Such, 123, Union Street, Boro', S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 4.4.11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Faithful Ellen. The little town's boy. Faithful Ellen. London, England; London: Printed and published by H. Such, 123, Union Street, Boro', S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 4.4.11; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Fearful collision at sea. The fearful collision at sea. London, England; H. Such, Printer, 177 Union Street, Boro', [1873]., Shelfmark: 4.5.6; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 20 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Female cabin boy. Burlington Bay. The plain gold ring. The plain gold ring. London, England; London: H.P. Such, Machine Printer & Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro'. S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 4.5.10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Female cabin boy. Burlington Bay. The plain gold ring. Burlington Bay. London, England; London: H.P. Such, Machine Printer & Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro'. S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 4.5.10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Female cabin boy. Burlington Bay. The plain gold ring. Female cabin boy. London, England; London: H.P. Such, Machine Printer & Publisher, 177, Union Street, Boro'. S.E., [between 1863 and 1885]., Shelfmark: 4.5.10; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Female cabin boy. Sally come up! Ramsey, T., Sally come up!. London, England; London: Printed at Such's Song Mart, 123, Union Street, Boro', S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 4.5.9; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Female cabin boy. Sally come up! Female cabin boy. London, England; London: Printed at Such's Song Mart, 123, Union Street, Boro', S.E., [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 4.5.9; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Female smuggler. Sir John Barleycorn. The willow tree. The female smuggler. London, England; London: Printed at Such's Song Mart, 123, Union Street, Borough, London, [between 1849 and 1862]., Shelfmark: 4.5.11; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 6, Folder 12)